[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "topic": "Semantic HTML",
    "question": "Which attribute is a must on the <code>html</code> tag if the site is in Hebrew",
    "answer": "<code>lang='he'</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "topic": "Semantic HTML",
    "question": "Which attribute is a must on an <code>img</code> tag",
    "answer": "the <code>alt</code> attribute"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "topic": "Semantic HTML",
    "question": "<span>What is wrong with this code:</span><code>&lt;h1&gt;Welcome&lt;/h1&gt;</br>&lt;h3&gt;A11y guidelines&lt;/h3&gt;</code>",
    "answer": "There is a skip in the heading tags"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "topic": "ARIA",
    "question": "<span>What technique can you use to give this button an accessible name:</span><code>&lt;button&gt;X&lt;/button&gt;</code>",
    "answer": "<code>aria-label='close'</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "topic": "ARIA",
    "question": "<span>What is the accessible name of this button:</span><code>&lt;button aria-label='Wix'&gt;Click me!&lt;/button&gt;</code>",
    "answer": "Wix"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "topic": "ARIA",
    "question": "<span>What is wrong with this code:</span><code>&lt;body aria-hidden='true'&gt;page content&lt;/body&gt;</code>",
    "answer": "Screen reader will not read the content of the page"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "topic": "ARIA",
    "question": "Which technique can be used to announce dynamic content changes to a screen reader user",
    "answer": "ARIA Live Regions"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "topic": "Keyboard",
    "question": "The tabindex attribute",
    "answer": "Cannot be greater than 0"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "topic": "Keyboard",
    "question": "What is the css property used by browsers to style the keyboard focus ring",
    "answer": "The <code>outline</code> property"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "topic": "Keyboard",
    "question": "Which method should be used when managing keyboard focus",
    "answer": "<code>HTMLElement.focus()</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "topic": "Keyboard",
    "question": "Which attribute should be defined on a non-interactive element in order to set keyboard focus",
    "answer": "<code>tabindex='-1'</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "topic": "Keyboard",
    "question": "<span>What is missing in this CSS code:</span><code><span>a:hover .tooltip</span>{ show tooltip }</code>",
    "answer": "<span>Focus state definition:</span><code><span>a:hover .tooltip, a:focus .tooltip</span>{ show tooltip }</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "topic": "Keyboard and Screen reader",
    "question": "Which flexbox property might create a disconnect between the visual order and the logical order",
    "answer": "The <code>order</code> property"
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "topic": "Keyboard and Screen reader",
    "question": "How to properly hide content from all users with CSS?",
    "answer": "<span>Using either:</span><code>display: none;</code><span>or</span> <code>visibility: hidden;</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "15",
    "topic": "Responsiveness",
    "question": "<span>Fix this CSS code to make the container responsive:</span><code><span>.container</span> { height: 100vh; }</code>",
    "answer": "<code><span>.container</span> { min-height: 100vh; }</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "16",
    "topic": "Motion and Animation",
    "question": "Which media query can be used to detect user preferences for motion and animation",
    "answer": "<code>@media (prefers-reduced-motion)</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "17",
    "topic": "Forms",
    "question": "An attribute that links between the form label and the input",
    "answer": "the <code>for</code> attribute which corresponds to the input <code>id</code>"
  },
  {
    "id": "18",
    "topic": "General",
    "question": "The name of the semantic version of the DOM created by the browser and used by assistive technologies",
    "answer": "Accessibility Tree"
  }
]
